SARTHAK JOSHI

PROFILE

Currently studying at The British College, Thapathali, who is also working at nKudos.com as a web developer, has an experience of dealing with user's requirement and give the satisfactory output. Sarthak has experience of working in online/internet technology companies and of completing challenging client projects. As a self-directed and self-organized person he is always pushing himself to deliver ongoing process improvements in anything he does.

PROFESSIONAL ACHIEVEMENTS

Programming and designing skills

Developing and maintaining the front end functionality of websites

Provide guidance to other team members on web development issues

Participating in discussions with clients to clarify what they want

Awareness of the Web Development industry, and new technologies

SKILLS HTML

CSS

jQuery, Javascript

ASP.Net MVC (Basic)

JAVA (Basic)

PHP

SQL

Blogger

Wordpress

WORK HISTORY

WEB DEVELOPER, NKUDOS.COM, CHAUNI, KATHMANDU

2014-9-7 to Present

CONTENT MANAGER (INTERNSHIP), KAMALDI, KATHMANDU

2014-6-10 to 2014-8-10

EDUCATION

KATHAMANDU UNIVERSITY HIGH SCHOOL, DHULIKHEL, KAVRE, NEPAL [2010-2012]

• A-Levels [Computing(D), Physics(E), Mathematics(E), General Paper(C) – 3.5- Credit Course]

THE BRITISH COLLEGE, THE TRADE TOWER, THAPATHALI, KATHMANDU, NEPAL [2013 - PRESENT]

(Foundation programme as a pathway to BSc (Hons) Computing)

•Academic English (I/II), Effective Communication Skills, Study Skills, Foundation Mathematics, Internet Technologies, Introduction to Programming and Computer Application

(BSc (Hons) Computing)

- •System Development (Database Basics), Web Development (Javascript Programming, HTML, CSS), Computer System (Number System, Fundamentals), Forensics & Security
- •System Development (Java), Internet System Development (PHP), Database Application Development
- *One more semester left to complete my bachelor level.

REFERENCES

I hereby declare that the forgone details are true and authentic. References will be provided on request.

Page | 2 Sarthak Joshi